visit: NFS31.XYZ
by @than Guavaberry
Zhang Tin Chi after losing to Ye Wen.
Bring Cheung Feng's child.
Get away from martial arts.
Already completed.
Two days later there was a transaction.
One crime
There are people who are worse than him.
Want him one leg.
No more work.
Little ones don't hit,
woman isn't hit.
The good is not beaten.
Hit this bastard no
breaking your rules.
Price doubled.
Consider for a moment.
Later it won't work anymore.
You're so great.
No more work.
Too bad.
I want to be an ordinary person.
There is nothing to worry about.
Wait.
I have a question.
You said your punch fast.
Or my gun is faster.
Outside seven steps.
Fast weapons.
In seven steps.
Beat faster.
Now about seven steps.
Stop.
Pay people to solve problems.
If you make sure money doesn't want anymore.
I respect you, go away.
You just behind the jacket
Feng, Feng-Feng.
Build school.
Fast wake.
What
Every day the porridge only added porridge.
Can't eat anything else.
Well.
Tomorrow I buy another for you.
Every time you say that.
Lie.
Thien Chi.
Morning aunt Liu.
Father, today is a good day.
Must be on time to get home from work.
Boss.
Just started work.
You think you want to go home from work.
Want to be lazy.
Come on, let's look at the delivery receipt.
10 bottles of soy sauce.
6 bottles of spicy oil.
Five bags of beans.
Help.
Aunt Liu.
I go between items, please
take care of my shop for a while.
Fine, calmly go / Thank you.
Aunt Liu I go to school / Fine.
Hey Chang Feng.
Let's go down.
Father, remember we have an appointment tonight.
After delivering the goods must
on time to go home.
You must remember going home
just right right on time.
Don't be your law teacher
don't obey, know no.
Take it easy.
The car has arrived.
Be careful, you know?
Bye.
Ah, you.
Hey Na-na.
You forget, pay money.
Sis Fei Long, old rules.
Kridit.
You've been crying a lot of times.
Today must pay.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow I will pay for you tomorrow.
I can't make a decision.
Come with me, meet the boss.
Jie Shao he has no more money.
Jie Shao.
Sorry Jie Shao.
Boss.
Who do you want to feel sorry for
Telephone.
Find people bring money here.
Today doesn't pay money.
I sold you to NanYang.
Become a prostitute.
Boss.
Bring me Batman, give me a look.
Well.
Let.
Want this.
Please wrap it up.
Eat.
Zhu Li Yes.
Apparently Zhu's brother.
I have brought the money.
Release the person.
Count it.
I warn you.
Later don't sell drugs to Na-na.
He is what I want to sell to him.
What you have to take care of is him.
You hit him this time.
I don't make calculations with you.
If there are other times.
I will definitely count clearly on you.
Wait.
Capital is already paid.
But the interest
Love me 500 more just leave.
My money won't be given anymore.
I'll definitely take it away.
I want to see.
How can you make us
Don't give money, don't expect to leave.
Catch.
Let go.
You're broken my stuff.
Get away.
Attack.
Police.
Don't move, don't move.
All don't move.
All brought.
Don't run away, don't move.
What happens, why fight
Police / Return to headquarters
just said, walk.
Sit there a little.
Name
Zhang Tian Zhi / Work where
Tian Ci Shi Duo.
Follow notes.
Zhang Tian Zhi
Huo ye dojo, black fist punch.
Ever been at Si Liang Chuan
Chang joined the battle.
And there are still records of arrests.
I just helped people at that time.
Then this time help people / Yes
He also helps people this time.
I did not talk to you.
I told you.
In a public place fighting
It violates the law.
You.
Sir / this is just defending yourself.
Let them all leave
This is an order.
No problem, sir.
Why do you want to fight
Release them.
Hey.
Why can they leave,
we can't go
Who are you
I'm Jin Ba Zhao's sister
apparently the Zhao clan
It's really troublesome.
You go.
Thank you, let's go.
Sir.
Then when can I go
Make him note new information
After completing note, then leave.
It's almost 10 o'clock still not home.
A feng / you're late / fast, still
hurry / return
me / don't say again.
Change clothes first / Know.
I change clothes / Hurry up.
Daddy fast.
Let's / your zipper is not pulled up
Come on, arrive, fast.
Daddy is a little fast.
Hello.
Sorry we closed.
Birthday, me.
Sorry young man.
All our chefs have come home tonight.
Okay, come back anytime, next time.
Next time back.
All your fault.
The steak is not eaten.
There is still a birthday present.
Wah Batman.
Daddy has no music.
It's been broken.
Really / Daddy doesn't
nothing, you love.
I am happy.
Boss, besides steak.
What do you want to eat?
Red grilled beef,
spinach is beef.
Beef tomato.
Why is everything beef
You with a cow have revenge
Well.
We eat beef restaurants.
We Zhang Le can be number one.
Not because we have many people.
Also not because of a lot of money.
But because of each of us
can trust each other
But I realized
right now there are people who are wiping out funds.
My father in life often said.
People don't believe.
There is no position
You still don't remember Uncle Xiong
Remember.
At that time I followed your father trying.
Based on this one two wound
I've taken three places for your father.
Now just take a little.
What is the problem
No problem.
Even though you're the first person to help.
Doesn't mean you can break the rules.
Take him home.
Today.
I have things to negotiate
with all of you.
Regarding the problem of Zhang Le.
My plan.
Black business now.
Changed nature.
In three years.
Zhang Le later.
Everything is clean.
This decision of yours.
Will influence our business.
Yes.
We strive in business
10-year-old black world.
Will not make a white road.
Make fake items.
This is where there is luck
bigger than us hijackers.
All.
I obviously can't guarantee a straight road can
the result is more than the black road.
I can only guarantee.
Everything starts now.
Will not be caught in jail.
Will not carry a fighting knife.
I see.
That is the opposite.
Right now Zhang Le is big.
Declaration must be.
It continues to be big.
So number one.
Great origin.
Black and white won't
dare to touch us.
If there are different opinions.
We decide through voting.
Who supports Zhang Le white business work.
Please raise your hand.
You're the boss.
You said it was right / Thank you all.
From now on it's all outside.
Will not move
The same heart tries.
For Zhang Le's sake changed his character.
Wow, Batman is great.
Batman turns three times
turn off criminals.
My father is better.
He can make a corner
defeat the bad guy.
She's Yung Chun's teacher.
Fuck Zhang Feng
My father is just a teacher.
He opened the dojo, Kung Fu was great.
My father also had a dojo.
My father is the greatest.
Past.
Your father only opens a grocery store.
He's a grocery boss.
Grocery boss.
Grocery boss
My father is Yung Chun's teacher.
Grocery boss.
Father.
visit: NFS31.XYZ
You won't teach Yung Chun later
Sleep.
Zhang Tian Zhi won big Yung Chun.
Daddy help me.
Father, I'm afraid / Afeng.
Daddy help, daddy.
Afeng / Fire.
Come on, don't be afraid.
My dad is scared / Come on.
Father here don't be afraid.
Daddy fast.
Right away / I almost caught fire.
A little fast.
Father how
Come here.
Let's cover it.
Afeng.
Afeng / Father
Dare a little, sit down.
Touching you, just touching me.
Today I will surely turn him off.
That is so, he can still run away.
You really can't
Father.
Father...
Burn him dead, fast.
Face this person must use all means.
Stop, stop ...
Please help me see my child, please.
thanks.
Father.
Afeng.
visit: NFS31.XYZ
Hey your son fainted.
Afeng.
He is hot.
Must go to hospital, fast.
Afeng.
Sis Cuin, Jle Shao is out of trouble.
Father is very sick.
You are patient, soon will be better.
I don't want to stay on
here, I want to go home.
You treat you to eat apples.
See.
thanks.
It is okay.
Please step aside for a moment.
Mari ah.
Little boy is badly injured, you guys
how to be a parent
Yes, Sir.
Understand sir.
This time it's clear.
This is a fire accident.
Come on, sir.
I know who did it.
I told you.
Accident / why can an accident
The house was burnt, and also chased.
You don't check
We don't need to teach the work police.
Street.
Father.
Our house is burnt.
Where do we live
I can help you guys.
My brother is boss Jin pa.
I bring you to meet him.
Your clothes are all burnt.
So buy a new one for you.
Meet the boss, use a little better.
Ms. Zhu's sister was so early in the morning.
Aming my sister / Brother Hu
in business talk.
You are clearly against me.
My guest is taken away by you.
I want you to pay money.
I work to lose, I want you to pay
money / I want you to compensate.
I want you to pay money
You two aren't right.
Bar Jie is the most important collaboration.
Drink this alcohol.
Later you can't fight.
You can't give in.
Drink.
What is wrong? Is there a problem
Not...
How nice, Sis Hu.
Tasty, we go first brother Hu
Ms. Hu's brother Zhu has come.
She's my friend Zhang Tian Zhi.
He found a little problem.
I want to accept them
Should not...
Staying in your house is too dangerous.
There are only two women, you want
stay, well live in my house.
Boy, come here.
You see for little kids to be scared.
How they live with you
Sorry.
Have disturbed.
Wait.
Brother, Tian Zhi ever
help me and Na-Na.
You taught me.
Friends must be friends.
Scared of you.
I told you clearly.
Two of my younger sisters.
One is my future wife.
You can't touch, don't think about it.
I will not owe you.
I'm at your bar at work.
Salary is rent / up to you.
Anyway, tonight's work time.
Come in.
Suppose here alone alone is okay.
Do not hesitate.
Na-na.
You like this up and down.
Use it less.
You use less than I normally do.
I when I dress less
I used to use quite a lot.
Really.
Daddy, big fire, daddy.
Father / Afeng.
Don't be afraid, daddy is here.
Nothing.
I'm looking for Cao Si Jie / He isn't there.
Street.
Glad to be able to meet, sign in.
Buy me a drink.
Buy me one drink.
Let.
I can't drink.
Hello.
Please drink
Thank you / let's just let me.
thank you
Lao Zhang.
Are you blind
Lift.
You got money from me.
I give you orders, you follow.
Take.
Sorry.
He's new, happy, happy.
Aqin serves a moment.
Let.
You, come here.
Zhang Tian Zhi.
Who do you think you are
The guest told you to take the scribe what a shame
There is no shame here
the price knows no
I raised it
The bar here has rules.
The guest is the highest,
You remember.
Let me / I can.
What are you reluctant about me?
Siao feng, you go to breakfast first.
Why porridge again
You're the first day of work at the bar.
There will be someone who is not used to it.
Slow down will be good.
In fact.
You hold back every day
anger, don't feel troubled
Our job is for happy guests.
Sometimes holding a little, will pass.
And again.
You don't blame my brother.
He is kind, afraid of you
guilty of westerners.
It's okay, I've forgotten.
Your father is afraid of being sick
Not sick.
Who did it
Zhang Tian Zhi.
Stop.
This is the problem of my smoking place.
I'll take care of myself.
This is Zhang le's problem.
I told all.
Don't make trouble.
In fact, you can't take care of yourself.
Let me take care.
Smoking place on fire,
let stop doing business.
You can't take revenge.
Not allowed to affect Zhang Le's business.
I for the sake of myself reply
revenge, is there something wrong
I'm not just revenge wrong.
Friends.
Turn off Zhang Tian Zhi's.
Bring Jie Shao home to rest.
Love him eat medicine.
I don't need you to pity me.
Follow him.
Please / treat this for me.
I don't drink alcohol at work.
I say I may.
Great Kungfu / Who are you?
My brother burned your house.
This is compensation for you.
Later you will no longer be in trouble.
I have also burned
your sister's cigarette holder.
This is compensation for you.
Later don't make me dizzy.
You talk to me like that.
You really have guts
What wind for you to come
I specifically came looking for you.
Meet your new friends too.
Tian Zhi.
Sis Jun, my helper.
I first followed him wandering.
Who doesn't know boss Zhang Le.
Cao Ye jun's name.
Ahu.
Don't say again.
Anyway, there's no brother Jun, there's no me.
If there is no business for me
go first / Zhang Tian Zhi.
You have a principle I don't force you.
What will you need later, anytime look for me.
Remember, don't blame again.
This is a check, consider paying a bill.
Sis Jun, I treat you to drink alcohol.
Great.
Remember when we were playing water guns.
Then play nuts,
now playing real weapons.
Shooting is very good, great.
Why
Young master Zhang Le.
There's still sister Jun, keep you dizzy
Now you also underestimate me.
I don't underestimate you.
I only speak the truth.
Shoot every shot, there is a price.
He is forever boss.
Forever press above my head,
whatever doesn't let me work.
I can still make big things
Who told you to get out late.
Honestly early on born you are the boss.
I told you.
Want to clean up the college.
It's easy.
What's the matter?
You don't come out trying, nothing is there.
You dare to think.
Maybe there is.
You seem to be okay lately.
What are you doing
Only a small business, you don't dare to work.
Selling drugs.
I don't dare
Want to work, you have to work big.
Wan cai is our Zhang Le.
Of course you have to go to the selling bar.
The place is the best, great.
I became a partner with you,
count in. I'm / you're crazy.
What colleague
Let your brother know,
I became a partner with you,
guaranteed the head will
feed the dog.
And again Lao Zhao at Jie Bar.
I don't dare to interfere.
Obviously not brave.
My sister is there, I'll take care.
Clan Zhao you don't dare
bother, I dare.
Well.
So friends aren't you help
me, I'm the one you help.
I became a partner with you.
We want to get rich, rich together.
Happy cooperation
let's drink alcohol.
Hey.
Rent this month, I already
say you won't be in debt.
Take it for your child, buy it
You give it to yourself / candy.
Every day pretending to be a principle
I saw the letter first
how come you have Yung Chun
Open duel with Ye Wen
even Ye Wen didn't dare to accept the duel.
Really great.
I want a duel with Ye Wen.
Why did the dojo close suddenly
Don't want to teach anymore / What
Your Yung Chun is so great.
I want to try, or we test once.
I don't remember.
You're pretending.
Let's make it like this.
Who loses, then the money
the winner's.
Power from below.
The one who came out was anger
I like to fight, can you take care
I'm this big.
No one ever slapped me.
You dare to hit me / You like to fight.
I represent your mother's father to teach you.
Bastard.
Hit again.
You scold people, they have to be hit.
You seriously fight with me.
You can't slap me.
Why don't you use Yung
chun fights with me.
I don't need Yung Chun now.
I'm your boss, you don't pay respect
I fired you home.
Your money.
Hey secret, don't say well
Don't tell people I lost to you.
It's gone.
It's still not burning.
Music Box.
Brother.
The wooden punch is not so hit.
This is it.
Siao Feng, you're great.
Your father taught you well
He taught me Yung chun,
but now I don't teach me.
Brother, I teach you Yung Chun.
Really
Then thank you teacher Siao Feng.
You see I'm not right.
Sorry.
It is okay.
I attach it back.
After all I use to hang clothes.
Walk on
Siao Feng brother every night
will come to the homepage see.
What's good at
see / see sunrise.
The sun rises to see the moon rising
Every day the bar lights come on
is my sunrise.
As long as the light is on.
All unpleasant things all forget.
So easy to be happy.
You are the person.
Simple enough.
visit: NFS31.XYZ
Glad it's so simple.
My example every day can be
do the things I like.
I feel very happy
You feel what I like / eat.
Dad said you were stupid.
He said you.
Father, who do you say
I certainly say you.
Two big kids hurt little children.
You're really angry.
I am most happy every day.
You can sing dancing in Jin Ba.
I feel here can
realize your own price.
When you find a world that is truly yours.
No matter what you can or lose.
You won't go away.
Nobody is willing or not.
Go or stay just choice.
But one moment of choice
you're just a moment of anger.
When you come back to see you will realize.
Leave today.
For the sake of the future.
Daddy can finally eat steak.
Afeng I patched today
your birthday.
Want to eat how much you eat.
I will not hesitate with you / brother.
People are out of money, you are out of life
Thank you brother Tian Zhi treat
we eat / Don't hesitate.
In fact...
I should thank you
on all new is true.
I disturb your life.
You have no conditions
thank you outsider.
Afeng looked after that.
I'm really proud to know
to you as friends.
Let me repeat to you guys.
Who do you think you are friends
Live in Bara Jie.
We are all one family.
Toast.
Happy Birthday.
For you.
Wah Batman.
I am in an orphanage so I like to volunteer.
There is a child made for me.
Thank you for your preparation, and
This cake is pretty / You're welcome
I still have to meet guests. Excuse me.
Please enjoy it.
Thank you
Welcome everyone.
Thank you for
your support for
advance the economy of Hong Kong.
We also have to return
to the community
Night auction results
this to build
back home
crushed by a hurricane.
so we can show it
on all our good intentions
And how deep is our wallet. (Finance)
This is the first auction
Antique flower pot Cing dynasty,
the initial value is five thousand.
10 thousand
12 thousand.
15 thousand
20 thousand
100 thousand ... is there a higher value
Sold! Please a generous woman
move forward and introduce yourself
Thank you Hwa Yang Foundation
give me this opportunity.
On behalf of the company Zhang Le. You
really hope the victims of the hurricane
and beg you all
give the best.
Zhang Le is a mob group!
You use illegal funds
for charity, refugees
hard to accept kindness.
Mafia businessman. If we accept him,
does not mean working with the mafia
We can't accept money
from criminal organizations!
Yes, that is true.
You, please come out!
Don't thank you here!
Please all calm down.
Miss, I'm sorry ...
this organization must unite
I have to respect their wishes.
They object to your background
We accept your good intentions
I do not live in an honest way.
I admit that.
Look carefully at your heart
You also make no difference. You
lying, cheating, and exploitation!
Are you willing to admit that
I do not think so!
Please give way.
Buy it here
Say it!
visit: NFS31.XYZ
The man named Fei Long sold it to me
Street..
Put it behind.
Wow ...!
Here's a lot
Cie Sou
We can get more
a lot of results from the Cin Hu region
Great. You are the one I salute the most.
Cin Hu, who do you think he is! I
absolutely not looking at it!
Take it
Discard the item
Ce Cia is involved in drugs
It should immediately tell your brother.
This problem is rather difficult.
My sister looks at my sister
Cing. Maybe he doesn't
can finish it.
This is the last one.
Hey, Mr. Davidson, I have come.
Mr. Davidson, nice to meet you
He is my good brother.
Cie Sou, big boss Zhang Le.
The biggest gang in Hong Kong. If he
join, will get more money.
You look
3 times.
I work with the best people
This steak has only one. Who eats
Boss, don't play with me.
This steak is very large.
We can share it.
What are you doing!
You think i don't
ever been held by a gun
Your weapon for
shoot the fuckers!
You say, every time
shots must be valuable.
My shoot is very valuable.
Apparently that's what your sister said
You really are useless!
If you kill me, you will lose
Many people can take your place.
Do great things
must like you, I like that.
You don't kill him, I'm still
will cooperate with you.
Sit ... eat ...
What do you think of me
"The right way, give the better"
But the heart isn't calm enough. It seems
You haven't practiced writing for a long time.
Over the years, so has strength
my father, your hands carry weapons, and blood
Right, I haven't practiced writing for a long time.
Now want to go back to the right path,
better than joining thugs.
At that time, you were a woman in place
your father's position, what is easy
As long as it's decided, no
nothing can be done.
It seems I just praise
Your kungfu is great, belittles you.
Today specifically wants to meet me, isn't it
just to talk, right
Se Cie is involved in drugs at the bar
How do you want to finish it
I want you to stop him / this problem
not easy. I will solve it soon.
Give me a little time
I am waiting for you.
Let me help you
All this because I used to be a drug user.
Now suffering from disease.
You can successfully escape from
drugs, it's not easy
Although now it can survive,
but I'm afraid someday ...
suddenly can't stand it
the temptation / We have long been
good brother, what trouble
who never experienced it
Isn't it finally able to handle it
You have to be confident.
Waiter, another glass
The Bon!
Thank you, boss / Good ... drink again ...
Not strong anymore. I'm really not strong anymore
Good, this is my girl
Once again
He stole our things.
No, I didn't steal it
You dare to steal my stuff!
Misunderstanding ... I didn't steal it
Run so fast! Want to report me
I really don't dare ... I don't know anything
This is smart. I will give
something good for you
Give me one pack
Brother Hu won't let you down!
I can be afraid of Cing Hu! Catch him!
You haven't been here for two months, right / Yes ..
Hey, where is Nana / Good, I'll find him
Drink it with me, come on
Nana ...!
I really don't use drugs.
I am right..
I know..
I know Nana.
Nana! There are people ... help ...!
You stepped wrong
This, I'm doing well.
Every time you do
mistake, my father
your law kneels
here all night.
Every time I will enter
quietly playing chess with you
So that you don't get bored, still remember
Of course remember. In fact
I hate playing chess
Because this makes me remember,
wrong and legal, those 2 words.
Why did you tell me to come here,
want to law me again
I'm always for your good.
In the past, you really listened to me
Why are you getting away from me now?
because I always listen to you.
Just know, I'm sister to Cin's sister,
don't know my name. Named Cau Se Cie!
But starting today, I don't
need to rely on you
Sign in!
visit: NFS31.XYZ
Se Cie! About drugs, it's not
your game! Jangna is involved
This path, I chose it myself!
Cau Se Cie, come out!
Sis, move on!
Get away!
You say give me time
Too late. Someone
killed at the bar because of drugs.
Brother, step aside!
Se Cie! Come on!
Great for Kung Fu! Fighting
with my gun!
Hit me!
His hand is my explanation to you
Sis Cin, lives are paid for!
If it continues,
I will destroy your bar!
Not resumed. But the problem
drugs, must be resolved!
Where drugs are hidden
We make a big problem, sorry
I stopped Kung Fu and opened it
bar, want to live quietly.
I remind you every time
myself.
How big is the difficulty
even have to hold back.
But for years
restraint, you could say ...
problems still arise. / I've been
thinking Kung Fu can make me famous
I even became a bat for
looking for money, then I just want to
become an ordinary person. I think I can
forget the past and kung fu
But in the heart, never let it go
We who practice kung fu, never
think the true meaning of kungfu.
You are openly challenging
Ip Man, how can I not
know the meaning of Zhang Tien's Kung Fu
Ce, you are really great
Ip Man and I fight
closed, I lost.
How can I lose / I lose
one move from him
one move, you give up
to yourself
You know, Kung Fu isn't it
for who is more
great / when you want it
know who is better
That's because you are not polite. I
I have wanted to beat you for a long time
This problem is up to all
Hong Kong residents already know.
The boss has ordered me
stop getting involved in drugs
For now, take it
your goods to another place.
Hong Kong is led by the British Empire.
Today one appears,
tomorrow will be more
people fight. How
you overcome that
How do I do business
From now on, who made the problem,
You do as I pay you!
Step aside ...! Police check! Turn off the music!
Men are separated
Stand right. All there
Here, fast! You are fast there
Stand up ... all, don't move ...!
Stand fast quickly
We can report,
someone is hiding
drugs here. You
must check this bar!
Sis ... / Don't make a fuss!
Sis Hui, I do business legally,
no need to play this big, right
The Caucasians themselves who are
lead, not kidding
Sir, heroin.
Motherfucker!
You harm me!
He is involved in drugs. Catch him.
Take him away.
The boss said you were involved in drugs.
Now catch you. Take it away.
Do not move...
Don't make trouble.
If not, get arrested!
You bastards!
Tien Ce! / Stand fast right
Police
There are people doing
burning, you say
accident. People killed
at the bar, you don't care
There is a drug dealer
real, you don't catch,
now it even slanders!
What kind of cop are you?
I don't know what slander is. We
talk about law. Live the orders of your boss
Can't distinguish right from wrong!
You don't feel guilty
with your conscience
I have no regrets. Innocent
with my conscience
Now there is evidence.
We can't catch people
Stop it I'm the boss of this bar.
You don't need to act.
What's the problem, me
alone who carried it
Don't make trouble
You let go of my brother. He doesn't
maybe hiding drugs
Relax, brother will be fine.
Wait for me to go home breakfast
Enter into the car / Search in another bar!
Good, Sir..
Already, don't look again, disband ...
Enjoy it. I'll wait outside.
Apparently you, the big donor!
This steak has been five minutes,
and the taste will be better.
Please eat. My food is far better.
Don't need your steak
You should enjoy
your last meal.
If i want you
eat, you have to eat
Chinese don't have a choice
People have the right to vote!
I choose to open the bar, you
choose drugs. Right, right
So you choose to join
mixed up with other people's business
You have chosen the wrong one.
Now you must die!
I'm wrong ... now it's new
know you seem to be a ***!
Actually the taste of the steak is very good now.
You waste it.
According to the police, Ms. Hu escaped
yourself, killed falling into a cliff
I do not believe.
I want to go somewhere first.
You can't go.
Don't block me
Nana is dead. My brother has also been killed.
The Westerner is still living well.
The police clearly know
but they just shut up! They just shut up!
You don't need to do anything,
as I will do it.
Daddy ... you have to go back.
There are things that you have to solve.
But father promises, will definitely be back.
Daddy, tomorrow, I want to
eat white cakwe porridge.
Wait for me
After leaving Shanghai,
we start from the beginning.
Hey!
Mr. Zhang
I can help
This is yours!
Don't carelessly accuse,
it's not mine. What about this
So what do you want to do, Mr. Zhang
I can definitely fix it.
You Chinese consider yourself great.
Just want to be a hero.
Did anyone tell you,
Heroes are killed faster
Sorry
Father will be fine.
He is my batman.
He can do it
defeat bad people.
I'm not here to be a hero.
I come here to beat you up!
Yongchun! Zhang Tien Ce!
Step aside ...!
What are you doing? Make a problem. Get out!
He hurt this person,
and damage the goods
Catch him!
Now you're accused, hurting people,
damage the things, we want to catch you
He is a drug dealer. In the car
those are drug items
You should catch
is him!
I saw him attack him,
and try to slander him
According to your boss, you are not only
hurt him, even slander him
We must arrest you.
What the fuck are two people fighting,
why only catch one person
He's a drug dealer, you don't
catch him. You receive the money
I don't know what you mean! I
here for order
You gather together
illegal, breaking the rules
Go home ... there's nothing to see!
Catch everything. You..!
Hit those bastards!
I found drugs inside
big amount in that car!
All evidence already exists. Person
it's a drug dealer!
What are you doing
I'm doing a job
as a police officer.
You protect the city
drugs, we were arrested!
You also want to
protect drug dealers
Let me go! I'm your boss!
You have no authority to do this!
Let me go!
Take him away / Yes / I'll give
explanation to foreign parties
That person escaped ... chased ...!
Father!
visit: NFS31.XYZ
Fei An, you disturb people again!
Why, want to be beaten?
I told you, my father
is Teacher Yongchun.
We also go to study
Yongchun. / Yes ... Yongchun's acting is great.